export const quiz = {
    topic: 'Child Rights',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is an example of discrimination?',
            choices: ['Helping a friend who is in need', 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color', 'Sharing toys with others'
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color',
        },
        {
            question: 'Right against discrimination',
            choices: ['Join in and make fun of someone different from you', 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly', 'Ignore the situation and pretend you didnt see anything',
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly',
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is an example of discrimination?',
            choices: ['Helping a friend who is in need', 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color', 'Sharing toys with others'
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color',
        },
        {
            question: 'Right against discrimination',
            choices: ['Join in and make fun of someone different from you', 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly', 'Ignore the situation and pretend you didnt see anything',
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly',
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is an example of discrimination?',
            choices: ['Helping a friend who is in need', 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color', 'Sharing toys with others'
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color',
        },
        {
            question: 'Right against discrimination',
            choices: ['Join in and make fun of someone different from you', 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly', 'Ignore the situation and pretend you didnt see anything',
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly',
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is an example of discrimination?',
            choices: ['Helping a friend who is in need', 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color', 'Sharing toys with others'
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color',
        },
        {
            question: 'Right against discrimination',
            choices: ['Join in and make fun of someone different from you', 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly', 'Ignore the situation and pretend you didnt see anything',
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly',
        },
        {
            question: 'Which of the following is an example of discrimination?',
            choices: ['Helping a friend who is in need', 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color', 'Sharing toys with others'
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Not inviting someone to a party because of their skin color',
        },
        {
            question: 'Right against discrimination',
            choices: ['Join in and make fun of someone different from you', 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly', 'Ignore the situation and pretend you didnt see anything',
            ],
            type: 'MCQs',
            correctAnswer: 'Speak up and tell a teacher or adult if you see someone being treated unfairly',
        },
    ],
}